Adriano Gaiotto de Oliveira

Address: 1283 50TH Avenue West, Vancouver, British Columbia V6P 1B1 **Phone:** +1 (672) 513-1816 **Email:** adriano.gaiotto@gmail.com

Personal Profile

Hardworking Java developer with 8 years of programming experience, currently studying Web and Mobile Application Development at Cornerstone International Community College. Strong technical and interpersonal skills that have improved in each step of my career. My greatest passion is in life is using my knowledge to solve problems and benefit other people and organizations.

Work Experience

June 2018 - September 2019 **Essence IT**, São Paulo, Brazil Java Developer

- Outsourced employee in CIP.
- Support, maintenance and upgrade to web systems using Java, EJB, JSF, Primefaces, Maven and Sql Server in Kanban agile method.
- Create System Documentation.
- Gathering requirements for upgrades together the client.
- Request changes and monitor the change process.
- Defend the change requested at the CAB meeting.

March 2015 - June 2018 **Stefanini**, Barueri, Brazil Java Systems Analyst

- Support and maintenance to Web and Batch system for Cielo using Java, JSF, EJB, JPA, Spring Batch, Ajax, JavaScript, Primefaces, Oracle and Weblogic;
- Monitor batch mesh;
- Participation in the project to equalize the new Java platform with the old Mainframe platform using Apache Kafka technology

January 2012 – March 2015 **Capgemini**, Barueri, Brazil Java Developer

- Support, maintenance and upgrade to web systems using framework of the client together with java, JSF, Struts, Ajax, Javascript, TomCat and Websphere;
- Integrate webpages of system with the Mainframe;
- Execute integrated and single tests in the system
- Create System Documentation;
- Create automation tools for development processes;

Education

September 2020 - Present

Cornerstone International Community College, Vancouver, Canada

Web and Mobile Application Development with Co-op

January 2008 to December 2011 **Universidade Paulista**, Sao Paulo, Brazil
Bachelor's Degree in System Information

Skills

- Programming: Java, EJB, JSF, Primefaces, maven, Javascrip, HTML, CSS, Swift, Python;
- Servers: Apache TomCat
- IDE: Eclipse, IntelliJ, Xcode
- Database: Sql Server
- Microsoft Office Package: Excel, Word, PowerPoint